<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<process>
	<activities>
	<activity id="0">
		<label>start</label>
	</activity>
	<activity id="1">
		<label>Locate and re-use designs</label>
		<verbBase>locate</verbBase>
		<object>designs</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="2">
		<label>Review previous designs</label>
		<verbBase>review</verbBase>
		<object>previous designs</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="3">
		<label>Update electrical design</label>
		<verbBase>update</verbBase>
		<object>electrical design</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="4">
		<label>Test electrical design</label>
		<verbBase>test</verbBase>
		<object>electrical design</object>
	</activity>
		<activity id="5">
		<label>Review previous designs</label>
		<verbBase>review</verbBase>
		<object>previous designs</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="6">
		<label>Update physical design</label>
		<verbBase>update</verbBase>
		<object>physical design</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="7">
		<label>Test physical design</label>
		<verbBase>test</verbBase>
		<object>physical design</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="8">
		<label>Test complete design</label>
		<verbBase>test</verbBase>
		<object>complete design</object>
	</activity>
	</activities>
	
<follows>
	<pair><pred>0</pred><succ>1</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>1</pred><succ>2</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>1</pred><succ>5</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>2</pred><succ>3</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>3</pred><succ>4</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>4</pred><succ>8</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>5</pred><succ>6</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>6</pred><succ>7</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>7</pred><succ>8</succ></pair>

	
</follows>

<text>
After the Process starts, a Task is performed to locate and distribute any relevant existing designs, both electrical and physical.
 Next, the design of the electrical and physical systems starts in parallel. Any existing or previous Electrical and
  Physical Designs are inputs to both Activities. Development of either design is interrupted by a successful update of the other
   design. If interrupted, then all current work is stopped and that design must restart. In each department (Electrical Design 
   and Physical Design), any existing designs are reviewed, resulting in an Update Plan for their respective designs (i.e. one 
   in Electrical and another in Physical). Using the Update Plan and the existing Draft of the Electrical/Physical Design, a 
   revised design is created. Once completed the revised design is tested. If the design fails the test, then it is sent back 
   to the first Activity (in the department) to review and create a new Update Plan. If the design passes the test, then it tells 
   the other department that they need to restart their work. When both of the designs have been revised, they are combined and
    tested. If the combined design fails the test, then they are both sent back to the beginning to initiate another design cycle.
     If the designs pass the test, then they are deemed complete and are then sent to the manufacturing Process [a separate Process].


</text>
</process>