<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<process>
	<activities>
	<activity id="0">
		<label>start</label>
	</activity>
	<activity id="1">
		<label>register</label>
	</activity>
	<activity id="2">
		<label>analyze defect</label>
		<verbBase>analyze</verbBase>
		<object>defect</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="3">
		<label>inform user</label>
		<verbBase>inform</verbBase>
		<object>user</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="4">
		<label>repair (simple)</label>
		<verbBase>repair</verbBase>
		<object>simple</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="5">
		<label>repair (complex)</label>
		<verbBase>repair</verbBase>
		<object>complex</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="6">
		<label>Test repair</label>
		<verbBase>test</verbBase>
		<object>repair</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="7">
		<label>Restart repair</label>
		<verbBase>restart</verbBase>
		<object>repair</object>
	</activity>
	<activity id="8">
		<label>Archive repair</label>
		<verbBase>archive</verbBase>
		<object>repair</object>
	</activity>
	</activities>
<follows>
	<pair><pred>0</pred><succ>1</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>1</pred><succ>2</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>2</pred><succ>4</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>2</pred><succ>3</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>2</pred><succ>5</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>4</pred><succ>6</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>5</pred><succ>6</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>6</pred><succ>7</succ></pair>
	<pair><pred>6</pred><succ>8</succ></pair>
</follows>

<text>
The running example is about a process to repair telephones in a company.
The company can fix 3 different types of phones (“T1”, “T2” and “T3”). The
process starts by registering a telephone device sent by a customer. After
registration, the telephone is sent to the Problem Detection (PD) depart-
ment. There it is analyzed and its defect is categorized. In total, there are
10 different categories of defects that the phones fixed by this company can
have. Once the problem is identified, the telephone is sent to the Repair
department and a letter is sent to the customer to inform him/her about the
problem. The Repair (R) department has two teams. One of the teams can
fix simple defects and the other team can repair complex defects. However,
some of the defect categories can be repaired by both teams. Once a repair
employee finishes working on a phone, this device is sent to the Quality Assurance (QA) department. 
There it is analyzed by an employee to check if
the defect was indeed fixed or not. If the defect is not repaired, the telephone
is again sent to the Repair department. If the telephone is indeed repaired,
the case is archived and the telephone is sent to the customer. To save on
throughput time, the company only tries to fix a defect a limited number of
times. If the defect is not fixed, the case is archived anyway and a brand
new device is sent to the customer.



</text>
</process>